Frances Benjamin Johnston Collection, 1935-1938 P0006
Frances Benjamin Johnston Collection, 1935-1938
- Frances Benjamin Johnston Collection, 1935-1938., Items: 2,280 images. Approximately 3.57 Linear Feet. Nine document boxes and five drawers in map case.
  - Warren County: Inez: Tusculum, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0416)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3108-3109.
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Coleman Jones House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0417)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3049-3050; Includes original (8x10) negative.
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Coleman Jones House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0418)
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Eaton Place, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0419)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3029-3032; Includes copy negative.
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Elgin, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 14 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0420)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3033-3038, NC3030.
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Elgin, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0421)
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Graham House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0422)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3040.
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Harvey House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0423)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3043.
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Johnston-Plummer House (Hudgins House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0424)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3045-3046, NC3048.
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Johnston-Plummer House (Hudgins House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0425)
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Mordecai House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0426)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3093.
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Pendleton House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0427)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2998-3000; Includes copy negative.
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Ruins of Montmorenci, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 29 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0428)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3055, NC3058-3060, NC3062-3065, NC3067-3070, NC3072; Includes original negatives.
  - Warren County: Warrenton: Ruins of Montmorenci, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0429)
  - Warren County: Warrenton: The Shady Oaks (Cheek-Tweety House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0430)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3110-3111; Includes copy negatives and Johnston negative.
  - Warren County: Warrenton: William K. Polk House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0431)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3099-3101.
  - Watauga County: Blowing Rock: Gragg Log House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0432)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2112-2113.
  - Watauga County: Valle Crucis: Mast Plantation Weaving House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 8 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0433)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3122-3123, NC3126.
  - Wayne County: Mount Olive: Kornegay House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 10 images (Printbox 8, Bwpprint P0006/0434)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC3112-3118, NC3121; Includes original (8x10) negatives.
  - Unidentified, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 5, Oimage P0006/0437)
  - Original 8x10 negatives, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White sheet film (8x10) (Bwfilmbox 1, Sheetfilm P0006/0438)
    Materials in this box have numbering that corresponds with Container Id's P0006/0001 to P0006/0435, materials that have original negatives are indicated in listing.
  - Copy negatives made from materials in the collection, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White sheet film (3x4/4x5) (Bwfilmbox 2, Sheetfilm P0006/0439)
    Materials in this box have numbering that corresponds with Container Id's P0006/0001 to P0006/0435, materials that have copy negatives are indicated in listing.
  - Deteriorated negatives made from materials in the collection, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White sheet film (8x10) (Bwfilmbox 3, Sheetfilm P0006/0440)
    Materials in this box have numbering that corresponds with Container Id's P0006/0001 to P0006/0435, materials that have copy negatives are indicated in listing, currently only includes one negative P0006/0323.